<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Resources on Facilitator Cards</title>
    <link>https://www.facilitator.cards/categories/resources/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Resources on Facilitator Cards</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is Uncopyrighted</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.facilitator.cards/categories/resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding Modularity to Your Facilitation Planning</title>
      <link>https://www.facilitator.cards/blog/adding-modularity-to-your-facilitation-planning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.facilitator.cards/blog/adding-modularity-to-your-facilitation-planning/</guid>
      <description>What do you do when an activity takes 15 minutes but you had 45 planned for it?
Or when your client tells you that you now have two hours, but you were planning for three?
Or when you&amp;rsquo;re not able to get any information about the people who make up the group you&amp;rsquo;ll be spending a day facilitating, until you&amp;rsquo;re in the space with them?
I could tell you what I used to do, but it involved a lot of scribbling and drawing of arrows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Go-To Facilitation Rider</title>
      <link>https://www.facilitator.cards/blog/go-to-facilitation-rider/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.facilitator.cards/blog/go-to-facilitation-rider/</guid>
      <description>Imagine you’re sitting down for a last-minute review of your facilitation agenda with your co-facilitator.
Scanning, they make a suggestion, “What if we did this activity like this instead?” and you think, “Yes! Good idea, let’s change it.”
Then you realize, “Oh no &amp;ndash; we can’t. I forgot to ask for sticky notes.”
Now you’re stuck debating whether to text your point of contact for the last-minute ask, to try to find time to run to an office supplies store, or to skip the idea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 Free Facilitation Tools to Boost Your Creativity</title>
      <link>https://www.facilitator.cards/blog/facilitator-cards-preview-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.facilitator.cards/blog/facilitator-cards-preview-pack/</guid>
      <description>No need to wait for the preorder: you can start using Facilitator Cards today.
We put together a Preview Pack to give you a sense of what Facilitator Cards are all about. In it, you&amp;rsquo;ll find everything you need to incorporate Facilitator Cards into your planning:
 12 do-it-yourself cards with facilitation tools to help your participants emote, ideate, clarify, and execute. An instruction manual for using the cards (explaining the theory behind them, and giving you some example use cases) 4 chapters from the forthcoming Facilitation Guide with detailed write-ups walking you through several of the processes Directions for printing the cards yourself (or getting them printed locally) Everything comes as a binder-friendly 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to the Facilitator Cards Blog</title>
      <link>https://www.facilitator.cards/blog/intro-to-the-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.facilitator.cards/blog/intro-to-the-blog/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re going to be using this blog as a platform to talk about a few things: the creation of the Facilitator Cards, how we (and others, and you) are using them, and other facilitation &amp;amp; training resources we feel compelled to share.
Beyond being a home to the cards themselves, our goal for this site is to serve as a gallery of related resources. Everything that falls into that bucket will be introduced on the blog.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>